<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Jesse McNichol&#39;s Research Website</title>
    <link>https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Jesse McNichol&#39;s Research Website</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a recent graduate of the MIT-Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution Joint Program in Biological Oceanography. During my PhD, I studied the biogeochemistry / ecophysiology of chemoautotrophic &lt;em&gt;Campylobacteria&lt;/em&gt; (prev. &lt;em&gt;Epsilonproteobacteria&lt;/em&gt;) under the guidance of Dr. Stefan Sievert. Currently, I am working as a Postdoc at the University of Southern California with Dr. Jed Fuhrman. This position is part of a larger project funded by the Simons Foundation to model the biogeochemistry of oceans on basin scales. From Nov 2016-Nov 2017, I worked at the Chinese University of Hong Kong with Dr. Haiwei Luo where I focused mainly on microbial isolation and single-cell genomic analyses. Before my PhD, I worked with the National Research Council of Canada on algal biofuels research in Halifax, NS, Canada. I completed my undergraduate degree in Biology on Canada&amp;rsquo;s east coast at Mount Allison University in Sackville, NB and am originally from Kingston, Ontario, Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jesse</title>
      <link>https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/jesse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jcmcnch.github.io/authors/jesse/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
